"National Land Control Point"
Day 3650
Today is my 3650th day
of loving Ling Yiyao.
Even when we're far apart,
we never stopped loving each other.
Beginning tomorrow,
nothing will separate us ever again.
Ling Yiyao,
will marry Lu Qinyang.
The wedding
is exactly like we imagined.
The sun is high in the sky that day.
A summer afternoon,
all of Nanjing is waiting for heavy rain.
Everyone is hiding in the shadows.
Except for Ling Yiyao,
who walks the whole city in her gown
to look for Lu Qinyang.
The wedding's starting, where's the groom?
Hurry, go find him.
Lu Qinyang...
Lu Qinyang... Wake up...
Get up...
Okay, okay.
Hurry!
Come here!
So many people in this world
I'm so blessed, all I have is us
The days and nights of this drawn out life
always make my thoughts drift far away
Ashen leaves drifting on a pond
Watching planes roar to some faraway place
The promenade of time, footsteps clamoring
The light comes, emptiness
with no one around
Come in...
Don't think about going anywhere.
You could just ask Majesty Yao.
Why do you have to steal it?
How can it be called stealing?
I'm just getting my game disc back.
She won't even play it.
Waste of resources.
Look over there.
Where's my "Counter-Strike"?
Found it.
"Must study English volume 5."
Day 01
I love you, beloved girl.
Seeing you, my heart beats fast.
The wind blows on hair so slender,
Caress me gently, enchanted eyes.
Dear classmate Ling Yiyao,
hello.
Since we parted two hours ago,
I've really missed you.
I'm Lu Qinyang, a junior from class 7.
I already mentioned that when we met.
My name is Lu Qinyang,
from class 7.
This is my first time
writing a letter to a girl.
I'm not very experienced,
but every word is true.
Right now, I'm listening to your tape,
imagining how happy this song makes you.
Give me my songs back.
I'm writing all this down
so that maybe you'll understand me.
First I want to clarify,
stealing the game disc wasn't my idea.
Although...
It was just you?
It was just me.
Fan Guanqiao went with you, didn't he?
I stole it by myself, really.
Alright.
If that's how you want it,
then every day during morning study,
you'll stand here as punishment.
For one week!
Well,
it's hard for heroes to
avoid misunderstandings.
But this jerk Guanqiao actually
liking your best friend
is totally unexpected.
I hope it didn't cause
you too much trouble.
Hello,
Fan Guanqiao, they call me Qiao.
Two years ago, I performed
well on the entrance exam.
I got into Baipu Middle
School and left home.
But I was too excited
and it led to slacking.
For now, I'm still not
on the same level as you.
But considering I was talented before,
then if I can have the right attitude,
be patient and not get ahead of myself,
I should be able to catch up with you.
Everything you do moves my heart.
Everything you do
somehow ends up involving me.
Damn kid!
Go!
Not standing in your
place and running here!
And that hair of yours.
If you don't cut it, I'll
get a razor and shave it off!
"I want us to be together"
I was so happy to meet you when I was 17.
This summer became a
warm one because of you.
And also because of you,
everything feels exciting again.
I want to tell you
secrets about this world.
Like how every day at 3pm,
a plane flies through the sky here.
It'll fly past at the same time tomorrow.
You'll see it sooner or later
I think of you at times like these,
and the future we'll have together.
Unknown number: Where are you?
Lu Qinyang: By the window
Lu Qinyang: Look to your right
Unknown number: Wait for me on the roof
Alright, class dismissed.
Goodbye, class.
Goodbye, teacher.
In order to rectify our campus order
and purify our learning environment,
today, we'll allow a repeat
offender of school rules,
a student unable to reform themselves,
to submit a total self-criticism.
Hello everybody, I'm...
Lu Qinyang, a junior from class 7.
I'm standing here today
because I wrote a love
letter to a female classmate.
This action affected her studies
and caused her distress.
I, Lu Qinyang,
have lagged behind in my grades
and haven't been focused,
and I know if I don't study hard,
I won't make it into a good college
and won't be able to find a good job
to provide Ling Yiyao with a good life.
Stop!
Be quiet.
Who said you could say that?
Lu Qinyang,
Do you have a single regret
for any of your actions?
I asked you a question.
I asked if you regret your actions.
Say something.
Say something!
What are you waiting for?
I regret nothing.
Day 1516
Hello?
Just wanted to let you know
I'm getting married.
It's like how we imagined.
There's an arch covered with
flowers and a red carpet,
and a white gown and black tuxedos.
All that's missing is you.
Ling Yiyao, you're really something.
Getting married tomorrow,
you're just telling me now.
You aren't worried I'll freak out?
Anyway, you're not the one I'm marrying.
If you can't make it back it's alright,
as long as you still send a wedding gift.
I'll be back in 10 or 14 days,
you can't even wait that long?
You said that plenty of times already.
A real men with character...
Can't you keep your word for once?
Wait.
Who's reckless enough
to marry someone like you?
Someone who can put me first right now.
Someone who's kind, responsible.
With a sense of humor.
Sometimes he get a little crazy,
but I still think he's pretty cute.
Why do I feel like you're talking about me?
So you have to wear a gown tomorrow?
Of course.
Then you better wear the running shoes,
because I'm gonna kidnap you.
Yeah, right.
See you there!
My mother's here, I gotta go.
Yaoyao,
You belong to me.
Say it one more.
You're mine.
I'm yours.
Everybody pay attention.
I've got two announcements.
Li Tao had perfect attendance this month,
so a 200 yuan award.
Wang Zibin,
is fined 50 yuan for
incorrectly wearing his helmet.
Our motto is
Surpass the peak,
Challenge the limit,
Always persevere,
until we succeed.
It's heavy rain again.
The dam broke again.
Overtime pay's an extra 200.
I'll be rich soon.
Bro, we should go back.
How we gonna work in this rain?
You're working yourself
to death for a wife,
why am I doing this?
Why are you doing this?
You're doing this for my wedding money.
Wait,
you're trying to ask
money from a non-adult?
That's not right.
Since when are virgins not legal adults?
Battery is low, please recharge
Let's go back, Xiaomeng.
Xiaomeng, can you hear me?
Xiaomeng!
Get out of there!
Brother...
Where's Lu Qinyang?
He just...
If I die,
please don't tell Ling Yiyao.
If I live,
then I'll make her my wife.
Yaoyao,
another 20 days and I can leave Zhoushan.
I made you wait too long for me.
That's my fault.
But does that compare
to a lifetime together?
Are you still going to blame me?
I've waited ages to see you in a gown,
can't wait to take your hand
and walk past all the jealous people
to our home in Nanjing.
That's my promise to you.
Lu Qinyang
is handsome and unconquerable,
and always keeps his word.
Where's your gown?
Aren't I supposed to steal you away?
You're already here, what's the rush?
Do you enjoy torturing me?
No.
Move.
- I'm sorry.
- Move!
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It really hurts,
Look at this, I'm injured.
Does it still hurt?
Yes.
Let me see.
It hurts!
I was wrong...
Let's see if you dare trick me again.
Fortune
Look on the other side.
Peace
What°Øs this?
You can't work dangerous jobs from now on.
And you can't be so far away from me.
Guess how much money I can make.
No amount of money is worth your life.
If something happens to you,
who's going to see my mother with me?
Are you serious?
We finally made it to this day.
I'm going to marry Ling Yiyao!
That day, Her Majesty Yao dragged me from
the school rooftop to the radio station.
Back then I thought Yaoyao sold me out.
I thought,
there's no chance now.
I didn't know it was
because I got on school TV
that Yaoyaoˇ
Auntie, I'll tell you a secret.
Yaoyao's English tapes from high school
were all switched to...
Even food can't make you be quiet!
I am eating.
How come there's so
many bones in this fish?
Auntie's dishes taste great.
The weather report says it's going to rain.
Lu,
go back home when you're done eating.
Don't get soaked outside.
Go, go. You're not useful here.
You come and make a mess of things.
Mom, if you want to say something, say it.
Don't be in such a weird mood.
What do you want to hear?
You think it through yourself.
Marriage is a lifelong thing.
If a man is not capable,
then in the end you'll
be the one who suffers.
He started working as soon as we graduated.
He works so hard,
I really believe in him.
What do you mean he's not capable?
We're still so young.
Being young isn't worth a damn.
I gave everything for your education.
Why did you even go to grad school?
The way he is, he's gonna support you?
He can help you settle in Nanjing?
"Lu Qinyang: It's really raning.
Stay home with your Mom one more night"
Stop, driver!
Stop!
Still hungry, right?
I brought you a chicken leg.
What are you laughing at?
Hey, let me say something to you.
Why are you crying?
Who's crying?
You're crying.
I'm not crying.
You°Ære crying!
I'm not.
I wanna to talk to you about something.
No problem.
I didn't even say what it is.
It doesn't matter what it is.
You might have to support me for a while.
If I don't support you then who will?
Day 1603
So, what price range are you considering?
Something under 800 a month is best.
This home is scheduled for demolition.
It's good for the price.
Washing machine...
Electric fan...
Don't go past the budget.
I feel like
there's missing something.
Are you nuts?
Lu Qinyang, we already have a home.
Fellow students, greetings.
On behalf of all the graduate tutors,
I express my heartfelt
congratulations to you.
I congratulate all of you
for becoming Southeast
University grad students.
Third Uncle,
When can the pay for
Zhoushan's project be settled?
There's been some urgent stuff lately.
I'll get the money to
your account tomorrow.
Thank you, Third Uncle.
I have another project later,
in Shanxi.
That's too far away.
I promised my girlfriend
I'd stay in Nanjing.
Right, I got a supervisor job.
Yeah, working to death for a customer.
There's a classmate gathering tonight.
Let's go eat together.
I won't go.
You guys go ahead.
Keep working hard.
Once you have enough for a down payment,
I'll find you a river view apartment.
"Available balance: £§ 8102.9"
Day 1620
Flourishing prospects,
Wishing you prosperity,
Everlasting friendship.
No, wait a second.
Ling Yiyao, what are you saying?
Everlasting love.
That's right!
Hey Lu,
You did Civil Engineering
at vocational school,
that counts as real estate development.
You have to grab the opportunity.
What's wrong with being a junior supervisor?
- You're right!
Let's drink.
They sell real estate,
he does construction. It's not the same.
Switch to a different line of work.
How long can you live
in this demolition home?
Doesn't he have to make
money to settle down?
Otherwise how can they eat?
Come on!
Take a shot.
Qianqian, what's wrong?
Still have business this late?
It's the director I met today,
they want to discuss a new project.
Oh?
Night shift?
What's my work got to do with you?
Just curious about your day-to-day.
Where should I pick you up afterwards?
What's up with you and Qiao?
Don't worry about him, Psycho!
He has been chasing you for so many years.
Do you like them or not?
I can't be with him.
Why not?
Who says I have to like whoever likes me?
The world's such a big place,
I have to choose wisely.
Also,
the way you and Lu Qinyang are,
it's way too hard.
Brother,
Buying an apartment?
Lu Qinyang,
I'll make you a bet.
Even if you can't buy an apartment,
Ling Yiyao would still marry you.
Do you know why?
Because I'm good looking.
Idiot.
You
found the right person to love.
"Down-Payment: £§ 300,000"
"100 days countdown to
completion of Binjiang Oasis"
Keep it up, keep it up.
When phase 1 is done,
we can finish the roof.
Come on!
Come on, come on. Get to work.
Why can't we pour?
Listen to me.
Call foreman Fang over here.
We still can't pour even you get him here.
What is it?
He won't let us work.
Mr. Fang...
You get out of here!
Mr. Fang, I'm not playing tricks.
We haven't passed the
inspection for phase 2.
We can't pour today.
Brothers, please help out here.
Let's try again.
I'm sorry.
Lu Qinyang,
Do you really believe I won't fire you?
Did you told us not to pour?
Mr. Hu, we didn't pass
the inspection, did we?
You silly kid.
Li Zhi,
help me take a look at my salary.
I just can't get these numbers to work.
What is there to look at?
You go home all the time,
you're lucky the fines didn't take it all.
I just made fish soup.
Drink it while it's hot.
A classmate said Qixia Mountain's
gingko trees are beautiful.
We'll go when you have time.
I want to live on the work site.
There's been some issues lately.
It's just me, and I
have to watch them work.
I promise I'll be back when it's done.
Hurry up and drink.
The soup tastes fishy when it's cold.
Ling Yiyao,
What are you doing?
I'm washing the dishes.
Can you wash later?
Oh.
Stop washing.
Alright, I'll stop.
It's hot...
Really, stop.
I stopped.
Ling Yiyao, you're something else.
Lu Qinyang,
you just wait.
Day 1800
Who's gonna supervise if you don't?
I've got a meeting soon!
Brother.
These rebar numbers aren't right.
And this one too.
"Men Are Dog"
The do note is off, here.
"Countdown to 2010"
Thanks. I°Æll manage on my own.
I've never seen you here, first time?
I don't really go out.
Same, I never go out.
You°Ære Qianqian's friend, right?
Director Shen,
flirting with the ladies again?
Is that show of ours a sure thing?
I'm about to look for others
with your beauty level.
What's the name of this
girlfriend of yours?
Is she interested?
Lu Qinyang: Having fun?
Ling Yiyao: Yes since you're not here
You're home, right?
Where are you?
Don't cry, I'll be there to get you soon.
If you're desperate then cry for help.
Help!
Let's go.
It's time to go home.
I don't want to be at home alone.
Don't you want to start the year together?
I'll take you back, come on.
I can sleep here.
This is a work site.
You've had class all day,
you should rest.
I'll sleep here.
See, it's comfortable.
Right?
Someone was chasing me just now.
I kept running and running.
I ran 3 streets until I got a taxi.
No matter what,
you're the first person I want to see.
But youˇ
How long has it been since
you've really talked to me?
I'm wrong.
I'm wrong...
You scared me half to death just now.
I'll take you somewhere.
This is where you work every day?
It's so high.
Welcome home.
Should I take my shoes off?
It's your home, it's up to you.
Binjiang Oasis, A luxury living experience
I built this myself.
Do you want to live here?
Coffee table.
Ouch...
Lamp.
I'm thirsty.
I also want a drink.
I love you, Lu Qinyang.
I love you too.
Day 1900
Say something.
You should sign the contract first.
I'll watch them and won't let them pour!
Hey, Mr. Hu,
Let's pass the inspection
first and then sign.
My conclusion is that we should sign first.
We have a very tight schedule.
It's worse if we can't complete the build.
Alright, talk later.
Coming.
Mom.
You're not coming home, right?
I've been busy at school.
Do you have enough money?
Lu took on a project recently,
he'll cash out at the end of the year.
We're planning on buying a home.
Good.
You're both capable.
You got everything set up.
In the future,
you take control of your own life.
But if anything ever happens,
or if he makes you upset,
don't keep me in the dark.
You hear me?
Hey, Brother Long.
- You're back.
You've worked hard, brothers!
Let's drink.
Bottom's up.
Mr. Hu,
Today,
inside my cabinet...
I got it.
Just look at your crappy little salary.
It'll take forever and a
day to make a down payment.
Lu...
I have to make a special toast to you.
I'll finish the glass.
Was there a misunderstanding earlier?
You upset?
Then let's move on, alright?
Making it on your own, it isn't easy.
Supervisors and the construction side
should help each other.
That's how opportunities open up.
The promise of youth.
Keep it up!
Have you ever seen such
an excellent supervisor?
Never.
He finally got it.
This is your good teaching.
It didn't go to waste.
Wait.
Lu, you're...
Lu, you...
You... you...
Hello, wifey.
Still not asleep?
Miss me?
Hello, Lu Qinyang? Where are you?
My mom is sick.
Your mom is sick?
I'm taking her to the hospital.
Hurry and come over.
Now?
Mr. Hu.
Mr. Hu,
Can I borrow your car?
My family's sick.
I promise I'll be back tomorrow morning.
No need,
take your time with your family.
Take the day off.
Be careful on the road.
Thank you.
Hello, Xiaohe?
How come concrete truck arrived?
Supervisor Lu,
they said you told them to come.
And they brought an audit form you signed.
This is abnormal in the
middle of the night.
Stop!
Who the fuck let you pour?
You son of a bitch!
I've put up with you enough.
Get the hell out of here!
Ling Yiyao's calling
Mr. Hu,
they poured the concrete.
What's wrong with pouring?
They didn't pass inspection.
Didn't they sign it already?
They didn't restart with our requirements.
Is that right?
Lu,
didn't you sign it already?
Right?
It's me.
But it's your...
If it's signed then it's already valid.
Right?
You told me to sign it
first, then how can I sign?
You're telling me now that I can't pass?
Lu Qinyang.
You're playing with me, right?
What do you want me to say to the customer?
I'm playing with you?
So what?
Nurse,
what's going on in that bed?
Which number?
NO.19...
Acute pancreatitis.
Does it need surgery?
Is it serious?
Not quite.
But she'll need to stay here for 2 weeks.
2 weeks?
Don't they need their own room?
If there were any rooms
then she'd have one.
Look at all these patients.
First come first served.
Mr. Chen.
Sorry to bother you,
waking you up like this.
Umˇ
Do you have connections
at People's Hospital?
Oh, alright.
Alright...
Alright, sorry to disturb you.
Hello, nurse.
Where did the mother and daughter go?
Mother and daughter?
They were transferred to a premium room.
It's this room.
Auntie,
Have Yaoyao call me when she can.
I'll come over and help out when I can.
So you don't have to surffer all night.
Am I right?
When I see you two,
it makes me remember
back when you are kids,
Yaoyao always followed you around.
You've grown up.
Made something of yourself.
Auntie, really sorry to bother you.
I had to do something, I got delayed.
I'll introduce you.
This is Lu,
Yaoyao's high school classmate.
This is Luo,
Yaoyao's childhood friend.
He just got back from Australia.
He started his own education company.
We got this room thanks to him.
Auntie, no need to thank me.
Luo.
You should call your mother later,
I want to thank her myself.
She helped me out at work when I started.
Is she doing well now?
She's doing great.
Yaoyao.
Wait a bit longer for me.
I'll work hard to give you the best life.
I'll make everyone envy you.
Day 1908
Qiao's calling
It's starting soon.
Where are you, Lu Qinyang?
Looking for work.
Brother...
You... you're really not coming?
You're too cruel.
If you didn't pick me
up then I'd be stranded.
Watch my eyes for a signal when you go in.
I pretty much settled it with Boss Xu,
he just wants to meet you today.
All depend on our luck.
Why are you finding me for such a big job?
Can't you belive in yourself a bit?
This job is important for the both of us.
Would I try and cheat you?
I heard you were a
supervisor on your last job.
What happened?
You quit?
I didn't agree with the
way they did things.
How is that your concern?
It isn't my concern.
Butˇ
I still didn't like it.
If I give you this jobˇ
then what kind of
guarantee can you give me?
I can't guarantee anything.
But I'll try my best.
I want to buy a home for my girlfriend.
Hurry and get a team together.
They have to start right away.
The first payment will come in 3 days.
Okay?
Brother.
All right...
There's 3 more rooms on
the 4th floor tomorrow.
Give me 1500 yuan for a deposit.
Okay.
Brother.
I brought them here.
Tired?
I should call you Boss Lu now, right?
Give us some opportunities
to make a big money.
Lu.
I've booked rooms for you guys already.
You can go and rest.
See you later, Brother Lu.
Brother Meng.
You're reliable.
As long as my brother calls,
I'll be there, any time.
Do you like it here?
I like it.
Do you want to work with me?
- Yes!
Make lots of money?
I really do.
Still thinking about Jiang Qianqian?
Just give up.
You can't hold onto her.
Go to pee.
Brother.
I don't know if I should say this.
You°Ære always using your own
money to cover the expenses,
and this project's so big.
If something happens...
Why's the TV off?
- What the hell?
These workers won't cut you any slack.
Who the hell are you?
You looking for trouble?
Turn it on.
What did you say?
Say it again.
Looking to get beat?
- What's up?
I burdened you again.
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
It's fine.
I'm glad I can help.
Hello?
Where are you now?
I'll be there soon.
What's wrong?
Stop here.
Thank you.
I am the people's servant,
helping is my duty.
Bro.
Qiao.
Lu Qinyang...
Yaoyao.
I'm watching.
It's fine.
Don't worry, Sister-in-Law.
We weren't fighting just now.
Lu Qinyang.
We have to make it.
We have to be amazing.
Brother Qiao.
Alright.
Get some rest.
Alright, Yaoyao.
Let's go!
Driver.
Slow down a bit.
I want to look at Nanjing at night.
Driver.
Can you turn it down a bit?
I want to sing a song for my wife.
Be good, don't fuss.
I love you
Beloved girl
Seeing you
My heart beats fast
The wind blows
The wind blows on hair so slender
He's fine, right?
He's fine.
That's enough, Lu Qinyang.
Lu Qinyang.
Alright, you can stop here.
Thanks.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Be careful on the road.
Wait.
What?
You didn't pay the fare yet.
I paid.
You didn't.
You didn't pay.
I paid.
We're home.
Thank you.
Drink some water.
I went to pay the hospital fees today.
How come there's no money in the card?
The money all went into the project.
Where are you going?
To look after my mother at the hospital.
I'll go with you.
No need.
You're worried she'll
be upset when sees me.
No.
Then the Jaguar is still
waiting downstairs?
"Gastroenterology patient Zhu Chunhua owes
£§ 5664.33 please pay by 12:00 tomorrow."
Hurry and go.
Don't make him wait.
Don't stay up too late.
Do you want some carnations?
Whatever you think is best.
This is selected from
140 cities in the world.
Based on safety, healthcare and education.
There's good benefits,
and it's full of culture.
The sky is so blue.
The ocean is even more blue.
Mom.
Why do you always ask him about Australia?
It's none of your business.
I always feel like
Australia
is a heaven for retirement.
I'm so jealous of your parents.
When you get well,
I'll set up a trip for you and Yaoyao.
I can only dream.
Xiaomeng...
We've been here for days,
haven't seen a cent.
Let's just go home.
If we don't get paid this afternoon,
we'll go find Third Uncle.
Brothers can't treat each other this way.
- Right.
Isn't this cheating people?
- I'll go out first.
You rest here a while.
I will be back right away.
Hurry.
Bro.
Did you get a hold of Brother Qiao?
Didn't he say the contract
was already signed?
The workers are all waiting
for the first payment.
If the money still doesn't come,
then I can't hold on to them.
Qiao...
Fan Guanqiao!
No one's here.
Where is this family?
I dunno.
Haven't seen them in ages.
Boss Lu.
How come you came?
Where are the workers?
They can't make it today.
We followed the contract.
First payment came 3 days after signing.
Just figure it out and start working today.
Then what do think I should do?
This concrete is here
and no one to deal with.
Then you solve it.
He can't go without unloading it today.
Alright, boss.
If he violates the contract,
he'll have to return the first
payment, and 3 times that for penalty.
We're going to settle up this account.
Boss Lu.
Don't think about running off.
Your home and your girlfriend's school,
we know where they are.
"Debt Notice"
Brother,
the workers all left.
Third Uncle called just now.
I didn't dare pick up.
It was definitely about the workers,
since they all came from his place.
How about we figure out
how to explain it to him?
Classmates.
All our Baipu Middle School alumni
are here in Nanjing.
Everyone is here.
Where's Qiao?
What's wrong?
Are you sure he's coming?
They sent me a text before boarding.
They should be here by now.
Why is his phone still off?
Jian Qianqian.
Where did this diamond ring come from?
Where else could it come from?
From Qiao...
Where are you going?
What's going on with you two?
Fan Guanqiao.
Where you running to?
I wasn't running.
I'm justˇ
A bit absent-minded.
Where did the money go?
I invested in bonds,
then I lost it all.
It was bad luck this time.
How much do you still have left?
I'm sorry, bro.
I'm sorry.
Why do you need all that money?
You're in that much trouble?
I was scared Qianqian would leave me, bro.
I can't stand seeing her
with someone else, bro.
I'm not good enough,
I'm not better than anybody.
As soon as I imagine her with someone else,
I want to fucking kill somebody.
I'm sorry.
Iˇ
I know it's shameful to beg you.
But can I ask you one thing, brother.
Just one thing...
Can you not tell Qianqian and Ling Yiyao?
Okay, bro?
Okay?
I'm begging you.
Brother.
I don't want them to know.
I'll pay you back even if
I have to sell a kidney.
But don't let them know, alright?
Alright?
Is he good to you?
Do youˇ
have any plans?
"Demolition of Illegal Construction Notice"
This building is about to be emptied out.
Where did you run off to?
I saw a few apartments near your school.
If you think any are suitable,
then I'll make the payment.
It's too expensive.
Let's take our time and look.
Or I can stay in the
domintory for a few days.
I'll pay for one then.
You know Qiao and Qianqian
are getting married?
Don't pretend to sleep.
What then,
are we getting married together?
Really?
A group wedding would be fun.
We can save at least half the money,
and I don't have to talk as much.
Qiao can talk and cry
non-stop for two hours.
Alright.
Let's just do it, I don't mind.
Such a pitiful wedding,
you're okay with it?
What are you doing?
I'll ask Qianqian.
Where is she having it? What's the budget?
You nervous?
It's fine with me.
But,
what about the Jaguar?
If you agree then it
can be the wedding car.
Save some money that way.
What about your mother?
I'll tell her after.
Well?
Are we gonna get married?
Say something.
I'm asking you, are we getting married?
Yes or no?
Lu Qinyang, are we getting married?
I'm sorry.
Do you still love me?
Third Uncle.
Brother Lu is here.
I'm sorry.
So that's it then.
You stole all my workers.
You know how much trouble you caused me?
You're pretty slick then.
Didn't I treat you well back in Zhoushan?
When did I ever forget you for a job?
Third Uncle.
I know everything I say is useless.
I apologize to you.
Whatever you want to do, I can take it.
I'm not the only one you screwed.
How much do you owe?
Can you even pay it back?
There's a wind power
station project in Xinjiang.
It's a long-term job.
If you take this job,
then the money you oweˇ
I can loan it to you.
Think it over first.
It's Xinjiang,
If you go then get the job done right.
You can't just come back whenever you want.
Take the blue one 3
times a day, after meals.
The red one is twice a day.
Don't mix them up.
Didn't think I would become a pill-popper.
At this age, nothing is more
important than being healthy.
And you, of course.
Hurry up and find a way to settle down.
I have to go on a trip later,
you can give her the contract for me.
I already explained it to her.
"Apartment Rental Agreement"
Later,
we'll go home to eat.
What do you want to eat?
Auntie can make taro braised pork again.
- Whatever.
Hello?
Ling Yiyao?
This is Qiao.
I have to confess something to you.
Give me the phone!
Yaoyao.
This bastard Qiao cheated me,
and he cheated Lu Qinyang!
The debt collectors even found me,
but Lu transferred the money right away.
Where did he get the money?
Is he really going to work in Xinjiang?
Hello?
Yaoyao?
Yaoyao, are you there?
Stop the car.
Hello?
Right now?
Stop!
Hello?
Lu, where are you? I need to see you.
I got an urgent job.
I have to leave right away.
I don't have time to help you move.
Where are you going?
Xinjiang.
Lu Qinyang, what are you doing?
If I didn't call you,
then you'd just leave
without saying anything?
It's a big project,
I'm not just working this time.
I'm an investor.
What are you doing?
This timeˇ
the job will take a long time.
I can't say when I'll be back.
Youˇ
take good care of yourself.
What do you mean?
Look at yourself.
All these years with me,
Everything I promised you,
I didn't do any of it.
I can't even take care of myself,
and I always have to think about you.
Really.
I already helped you decide.
It's a bad deal.
Are you trying to break up with me?
Aren't you going to Xinjiang?
I'll wait for you.
I'll just act like you're joking.
I'm sorry, it's not a joke this time.
Yaoyao.
In my heart, you've always been the best.
You should be blessed and envied,
you don't deserve to be treated like this.
If you've been hurt
because you followed me,
I'll never forgive
myself as long as I live.
From now on,
I won't walk this road with you.
Lu Qinyang!
Day 3330
Are there any other services you need?
No, that's all.
You can help by rating my service.
Alright.
Thank you.
Director Chen,
it's time for the second payment.
Yes. It hasn't been easy.
All the brothers have worked hard,
and you know this weather has been shitty.
Coordinates?
How can the coordinates be wrong?
You already checked all the numbers.
Then this means we wasted our time.
Hello?
Make a call and test it.
"Ling Yiyao"
Sorry, this number is no longer in service.
See, this is a Cantonese restaurant.
The dishes are alright,
and the owner gets along
great with your Uncle Luo.
The wedding banquet can
be here, how's that?
I think it's pretty nice.
See?
It's good, it's good.
Chinese restaurants are the best,
you see that, Son?
I knew Yaoyao would agree.
- That's the most important.
Just look.
Just think, all these years.
I thought,
that's the end of the road for us.
But now,
these kids have brought us together again.
That's right.
Move it 10 centimeters to the left.
Move back, aboutˇ
4 steps.
Hello, please sit.
Miss, help me put this money on this card.
Teacher Yao.
You'reˇyou'reˇ
Lu Qinyang,
wrote that love letter to you.
Right?
Can't remember the name of
a good student like you.
But a damn rascal, his
name I remember clearly.
That damn kid,
he ticked me off plenty back then.
I think I still have your
love letter somewhere.
I'll go back to look for
it, I'll send it to you.
Teacher, I'll go make a copy of your ID.
The turbine isn't spinning again.
The wind is too big, don't fix it.
We'll check tomorrow, just come back.
The fucking power's out again,
isn't that funny?
We're supposed to be generating power.
Water...
Today is the 1337th day
I've been in Xinjiang.
And it's my 1338th day
of missing Ling Yiyao.
40 days ago,
we broke the only mirror in the worksite.
Nobody misses it.
Workers from Jiangsu,
Sichuan,
Henanˇ
These hundred men look more and more alike.
The face of the one called Lu Qinyang
has become ever more invisible.
Soon he might even forget himself.
I hope you can still remember.
The blue cable is brought over
from our original coordinates.
The red cable came from the client.
They said our coordinates weren't accurate.
It's getting worse, we
have to measure again.
Bullshit!
What the hell are they talking about?
They're just playing with us...
Be quite!
They approved it to begin with.
My bro lugged the EDM
and tested every point.
Are they messing with us on purpose?
So what if they're doing it on purpose?
You don't want to get paid?
We'll just do it again, shut them up.
Brother, wait for me another 2 days.
I can definitely fix it.
No need, I can do it myself.
There's no GPS,
and you have to lug a 20 kilo EDM with you.
Hello?
The warm weather is fine.
- Hellol
Hello?
Who knows what the weather will be like?
Who heard the weather report?
Yaoyao.
Can you hear me?
It cuts in and out.
The signal tower here is bad,
still hasn't been fixed.
I saw the news,
it's snowing over there.
It's snowing in the north.
Where I'm at,
it still hasn't snowed.
Hello?
Yaoyao?
I'm here.
Are you doing okay?
- Are you doing okay?
I'm pretty good.
That's good.
I'm going to work.
I'm a bank clerk.
Didn't you used to say that kind of job
was like being a shop window model?
Yeah?
I don't even remember.
Lu Qinyang.
I'm getting married.
It's like how we imagined
There's an arch covered with flowers
and a red carpet,
and a white gown and black tuxedos.
All that's missing is you.
Wait.
Who's reckless enough
to marry someone like you?
Someone who can put me first right now.
Someone who's kind.
Brave.
Responsible.
With a sense of humor.
Sometimes they get a little crazy,
but I still think they're pretty cute.
Why do I feel like you're talking about me?
Then you better wear the running shoes,
because I'm gonna kidnap you.
Yeah, right.
Anyway, I gotta go, Lu Qinyang.
I have to go somehwere far, far away.
I won't ever come back.
I want to see you.
I said I want to see you, Yaoyao.
I've never given up,
I've always tried hard.
Liar.
When you did your self-criticism,
you told thousands of people
that you'd work hard to provide
Ling Yiyao with a good life.
And you say you don't regret it.
I never regretted it, Yaoyao.
I just want you next to me,
that's the good life I want.
Yaoyao.
I°Æve been suffering every single day here.
I shouldn't have left you three years ago.
I should be a bit braver.
Wait for me, I'll go back right now.
Bro, you're doing coordinates
with your luggage?
I'm gonna find Ling Yiyao.
I°Æll meet her in Jiayuguan.
I°Æll beg her to forgive me.
And then I'll ask her to marry me.
Really?
Don't worry about the coordinates.
I'll finish them and then leave.
Emergency Warning.
This is the city weather report station.
2 major low pressure
currents are moving south,
with a severe incoming snowstorm
What kind of weather is this?
Where's Lu Qinyang?
"National Land Control Point"
Lu,
don't get out of the car.
We're on our way to your coordinates, okay?
Wait for us in the car.
Lu, do you copy?
Lu Qinyang, do you copy?
LuˇLu Qinyang, do you copy?
Lu?
Ling Yiyao: I'm here,
waiting at the station
Brother!
Lu!
Third Uncle,
we're at the coordinates.
We don't see him.
Meng,
get all the brothers over here.
Send a flare for Lu.
Lu!
Yaoyao,
I'm here, where are you?
I'm at the entrance hall, where are you?
I don't see you.
Where are you?
Hello, Lu Qinyang?
How come you're so late?
I almost didn't make it.
If I waited any longer,
I'd find someone random and marry them.
Ling Yiyao.
You're the one I moved
heaven and earth for.
There's thousands of witnesses.
From now on,
there's only you not wanting me.
Because I'll always want you.
Come on,
I'll take you back to Nanjing.
Ling Yiyao.
We've been together 10 years.
Shouldn't you be
proposing to me?
It's just like a dream.
The groom is getting cocky,
doesn't even come out to welcome us.
It's about to start downstairs,
soon!
I forgot the bowtie.
Lu Qinyang!
Lu Qinyang... Wake up...
Lu Qinyang...
If I die,
don't tell Ling Yiyao.
If I live,
then I'll make her my wife.
Lu Qinyang: Yaoyao, are
you still waiting for me
Sendingˇ
Message failed to send!
Sorry, the number you
dialed is not in service.
Please try again later.
Day 3651
Lu!
"If I die, don't tell Ling Yiyao!"
"Message successfully sent"
Lu Qinyang: Yaoyao, are
you still waiting for me
Ling Yiyao: Stupid...
"Lu Qinyang: I fell asleep and dreamed
you were wearing a beautiful gown"
"Lu Qinyang: I thought of your fish soup you
have to make it when I'm back in Nanjing"
"Lu Qinyang: Yaoyao, I'm sorry
I'm late again"
"Lu Qinyang: It's snowing heavy,
I'm a bit lost wait for me"
"Unread Message"
Lu Qinyang: I feel like a snowman, cool huh
Lu Qinyang: The snowman fell down
"Lu Qinyang: Yaoyao, find some place warm
don't come out no matter what"
Message failed to send!
"Lu Qinyang: The wind stopped, the snow
stopped it feels so warm, like summer"
Lu Qinyang: Talk with me,
it's so lonely by myself
"Lu Qinyang: I saw meteors passing by
Yaoyao, may the happiness be with you"
"Lu Qinyang: I'm not good
enough in these ten years Sorry"
"If I die, don't tell Ling Yiyao!"
"If I life, then I'll make her my wife!"